I'm Miwa.
Miwa, huh?
I'm Momo...
"Momo"?
Well, call me whatever.
How about... Momotaro?
Okay.
So?
I was... molested.
Yeah?
It was the same person every day.
One day, I gathered up my courage and grabbed his arm.
I shouted for help.
Did it work out?
Yes. Everyone around us pinned him down for me.
I'm glad.
But why me? I'm not even that feminine.
I don't really get it.
Yeah.
I'm not, right?
That's not true.
Really?
But that guy was an executive at my dad's company.
Huh?
My dad got fired.
My mom asked why I couldn't just put up with it.
She said being groped just shows how cute I am.
That he picked me because I'm so cute.
Calm down. None of that is your fault.
It's not your fault, okay?
Momotaro.
Don't worry. I'll protect you.
Thank you.
Sure.
You have broad shoulders.
Not really.
Ai!
We can't just run away!
What else am I supposed to do?
Yeah, we've got to fight!
I can't in this mist!
Besides, on my own...
Ai!
Ai.
Could you use this for something?
Mine, too.
Penlights?
Thanks.
This'll do it.
All right! Come at me!
You want me to touch you!
Adults can tell!
Tell me how much you want it!
Just touch your wife!
You got married because you love each other!
Come out already!
No thank you.
Ai!
Are you okay?!
Don't let your guard down.
Oh, no!
What'd you rather be?
Skewered, or turned to stone?
Neither!
Skewered it is, then!
Females have expiration dates!
Momotaro!
Don't come out.
You're a perverted brat who loves being touched.
Come on; I'll make you feel real good.
Bastard.
Fine.
You can touch me.
Miko, Mako.
What's this song?
A real Yu-Yu fan couldn't skewer another fan
while Yu-Yu is watching!
Ai, raise the penlights!
Wave them!
Don't be shy!
Way to go, Mako!
That's amazing!
I've got to go after her!
I was actually excited.
It was, like, thrilling and suspenseful.
Plus,
you did it because I'm cute, right?
Of course I did.
Finally, we understand each other.
Ai.
Yeah.
Be gentle, okay?
But of course.
Come on, hands up.
Touch me.
Now I'm really mad!
Get lost!
You tricked me!
Of course I did.
I'd rather die than be with you.
Women... are quick to deceive.
Just kidding.
Watch out!
Idiot!
Stupid brats are all just prey to adults!
I'll hit you with a shot to the heart!
Rika?!
We're immortal in this world.
So, we get fixed over time.
Oh, yeah!
Let's get this over with.
Sure.
We a unit again?
Yeah!
Don't you want to go colorfully?
Don't you want to go colorfully?!
Take that!
And that!
Ready...
Go!
You overdid it.
It was just one day, but I fell in love with you.
Thank you.
I'm really glad that I got to meet you.
Can I stay like this until I disappear?
Sure.
I'm beat.
Yeah! She's getting warmer.
We've become fans of you two!
Totally! I'd come running to see your debut.
No way. I'm not having a debut.
We're your number one fans.
Yeah!
Bye-bye!
It's just too soon to discharge you.
Getting your muscles back in shape takes time.
Thank you very much.
You got out early, huh?
Thanks to you and the Egg.
It seems like fighting there puts
a heavy strain on our bodies.
Like high-altitude training?
Yes.
Now that you mention it, I think
I've gotten some definition on my abs.
Why not join a sports club and test them out?
Oh, but you don't go to school, do you?
It's not like school is all there is.
But my mom expects me to go.
I don't go to school either.
And no one complains?
Not really.
Wow.
Where to next?
I thought I'd go buy an Egg.
Mind if I join you?
Of course not.
Neiru?
Get in.
I've got to make a stop first.
O-Okay.
Oh, yeah, about Rika.
She's not so bad.
I see.
I guess she's contrarian, or her
attitude doesn't match her feelings.
Isn't she out to get her "wallet" back?
Nah.
That's just what she says. I think.
Let's hope so.
It's huge.
Your dad's work?
You're trusting, Ai. You forgive easily.
You mean, what I said?
Yes.
I guess so. I'm hopeless that way.
You're lovely that way.
You're hopeless and lovely that way.
We need someone like that
sometimes, or we'll never be saved.
Welcome back, Ma'am.
Okay. This is my friend, Ohto Ai.
This is my first secretary, Tanabe Misaki.
Hello, Ms. Ohto.
Hello.
Congratulations on your recovery, President.
Thanks.
President?!
There are other girls tackling Eggs.
Like who?
A sunflower, I guess.
Excuse me?
You'll see.
They're a bit eccentric,
but they're all good kids. Try to make friends.
A sunflower, huh?
You've never eaten French fries?!
No.
They're crunchy and super tasty when they're hot.
Not so great cold, though.
Is that so?
Oh, but you know, there's a trick
to reheating them in the oven.
This is a women-only car!
Stupid man! If you want to ride, get it out!
I'll chop it off for you!
I have a right to ride in this car, too!
What're you trying to say?!
I'm saying
that I'm a girl, too!
No way!
Get lost!
Momotaro.
My real name is Momoe. Sawaki Momoe.
You really are a girl, right?
I didn't mean to trick you.
Don't you think a masculine style suits me better?
It doesn't matter.
Even if you're a girl, I've still fallen in love with you.
I love you. I don't want to disappear.
I want to stay with you forever.
Yeah. You're warm.
There are more than you'd think, Haruka.
Girls like you, who say they love me.
Touch me.
I forgot my wallet.
Would you mind—
I would.
You don't bring it on purpose.
My daddy says a beautiful woman shouldn't carry a wallet.
Plus, my little wallet's running late.
Ai isn't your wallet.
I'm joking.
Then stop. It's not funny.
What?
E-Excuse me.
I'm—
Wow, you're handsome!
Like a host!
A host?
So, there are guys, too.
That makes sense. Boys kill themselves, too.
Acca, what's going on?
There should be no boys.
Yes. Boys' and girls' suicides mean different things.
Men are goal-oriented, women are emotion-oriented.
Women are impulsive and easily
influenced by others' voices.
Like human relationships?
That's part of it.
Imagine a "temptation of death."
A temptation of death?
Scary.
But I think I kind of get it.
Some might be led astray by the temptation and regret it.
This place exists for those who want to
return children like that to life.
So, don't get hung up on gender.
Yeah, you shouldn't discriminate!
What?!
Umm...
Are you okay?
Oh, I'm...
I mean...
I'm...
Right now, what do I look like to you?
Huh?
Like a crying girl.
Really?
A crying girl... who looks like a model.
A sunflower.
This? It's my favorite, so it's practically all I wear.
But...
it's really cute.
Thanks!
Models all have amazing contours
from their necks to their collarbones.
You know a lot?
A bit. I saw models a lot when I was little.
Yeah?
My mom used to be editor-in-chief of a fashion magazine.
Oh! Neiru! Come look.
Isn't her neck super pretty?
It's like a model's.
You're right. It's long and slender.
And no Adam's apple.
You like Adam's apples, too, right?
Me, too.
I like Adam's apples, too! They're sexy.
Aren't they, though?!
They seem so firm!
I know what you mean!
I don't!
How about my neck, then?
Isn't it nice and inviting?
Like a puppy.
A puppy? A puppy?!
Bow-wow-wow, lend me some cash.
Dummy.
Hey, don't laugh.
But... Sorry.
You're laughing too much.
Come on, let's go buy Eggs.
Sure.
Hey, what's your name?
Me? Sawaki Momoe.
Huh?
Sawaki?
To be continued.